Finding Aid for the George Peabody College Photograph Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series XVI: Portraits
  - F
    - Finnie, Jean
    - Fisher, Amelia Catherine
    - Fisher, Connie
    - Fisher, Edgar J.
    - Fisher, Morrell
    - Fisher, Paul G.
    - Fitch, Hubert V.
    - Fite, Elwin
    - Fitzgerald, Kathryn
    - Fitzgerald, Rufus H.
    - Fitzgerald, William
    - Fitzpatrick, Mrs. W. J.
    - Flack, Elmer E.
    - Flanagan, Beecher
    - Flemming, Howard
    - Fletcher, Leonard J.
    - Fletcher, Nancy
    - Fletcher, Ruth M.
    - Fletcher
    - Fling, H. H. J.
    - Flinton, Margaret
    - Flora, Ben V., Jr.
    - Floyd
    - Flunderbuk, R. S.
    - Follis, Hattie
    - Folsom, Elizabeth G.
    - Foote, Bruce
    - Foote, John
    - Force, William
    - Ford, Frederick A.
    - Ford, Henry
    - Ford, Jeanne
    - Forster, Virginia
    - Fort, Gareth E.
    - Forte, Ewing
    - Forte, Jane
    - Foster, Craig
    - Foster, W. H.
    - Fountain, A. M.
    - Fountain
    - Fox, Jesse Wells
    - Frame, Ruth
    - Frank, Dorothy Jean
    - Franks, Sir Oliver Cromwell
    - Frase, John M. (2)
    - Fraser, Lily Paul
    - Frazier, Alexander
    - Frazier, C. O.
    - Freeman, Douglas Southall
    - Freeman, Elsa S.
    - Freeman, P. B.
    - Frick, William
    - Friedman
    - Fritts, Ross
    - Fulghim, B. E.
    - Fuller, Jimmy
    - Fuller, Melville W.
    - Funston, G. Keith
    - Fusco, Gene C.
    - Fussell, James
  - G
    - Gaines, Joyce Donelson
    - Gaithey, Vivian
    - Galbraith, Ronald
    - Gannaway, Mary ann
    - Gannaway, Richard M.
    - Garrett, Leon
    - Garrison, Frank
    - Garrison, Harrell E.
    - Garrison, Karl C.
    - Garrison, Sidney C.
    - Garrison, Sarah
    - Garwood, Modena
    - Gary, Roland Thacher
    - Gatwood, Barbara
    - Gatwood, Elden J.
    - Gatwood, Robin F.
    - Gaylord, Charlotte H.
    - Gebhart, G. B.
    - Gee, James G.
    - George, Edna
    - George, J. B.
    - George, N. L.
    - George, Paul
    - Gerber
    - Gerst, Gerri
    - Gibbs, Minnie
    - Gibbs, Polly
    - Gibson, Foye G.
    - Gibson, I. H.
    - Gibson, Joseph C.
    - Gibson, Joseph E.
    - Gibson, Roberta
    - Gibson
    - Giddings, Peggy
    - Giles, Pearllie
    - Gill, Rexie
    - Gillespie, Ruth
    - Gillentine, Flora M.
    - Gillette, Frank E.
    - Gillette, Mrs. Frank E.
    - Gilliland, Emma Dim
    - Gilman
    - Gilreath, Nancy Ready
    - Gilstrap, Robert
    - Ginger, George
    - Gingold, Josef
    - Ginzberg, Eli
    - Gipson
    - Gitler
    - Glace, Margaret
    - Glazier, Esther B.
    - Gleaves, Edwin
    - Glenny, Hazel
    - Glover, Aristine
    - Godwin, Winfred L.
    - Golden, Pearl
    - Goldie, Cathy
    - Goldschmidt, Martha Irene
    - Gointer
    - Gonzales, Clara B.
    - Gooch, Fankie
    - Gooch, Margaret
    - Good, Sayler
    - Goodman, Fannie
    - Goodyburty
    - Gordon, Marguerite D.
    - Gore, Albert, Sr.
    - Gore, Johnnie
    - Gore, L. Lawton
    - Gore, Tipper
    - Gorodetsky
    - Goslin, Willard (2)
    - Goulding, R. L.
    - Grace, Mary Jane
    - Grace
    - Gracy, Irene
    - Gracy, Martha Moore
    - Graham, Carmen
    - Graham, Charles C.
    - Grant, J. R.
    - Grass, Louise
    - Gravel, H. O.
    - Graves, John Temple
    - Graves, Octavia W.
    - Gray, William S.
    - Green, Edith
    - Green, Julia
    - Greenberg, Norman
    - Greene, Hattie Bryant
    - Greene, Mande
    - Greene, Patricia
    - Greer
    - Gregor, Howard
    - Grew, Joseph C.
    - Griffin, Hazel
    - Griffin, Margaret
    - Griffin, William
    - Griffith, Helen Livingston
    - Griffith, P. H.
    - Griggs, F. C.
    - Grigsby, Frances Cate
    - Grigsby, J. B.
    - Grime, Sara Lois
    - Grise, Finley
    - Grise, George C.
    - Grisham, Frank
    - Grole, Hobart J.
    - Groomes, Stella Mae
    - Gross, Jane
    - Gross, John
    - Grove, J. G.
    - Growley, Dorothy
    - Grueter, Tresa
    - Guardia, J. E.
    - Guess, John
    - Guffey, Elizabeth C.
    - Gunn, Eric M.
    - Gunnoe, Otway
    - Gwaltney, Jesse W.
  - H
    - Hackworth, W. S.
    - Haddox, Clara
    - Hagenah, William J.
    - Haggard, E. M.
    - Haines, Marian
    - Hakim, Letitia
    - Hakim, Maurice
    - Hakim, Soghrat
    - Halbert, Mrs. Jimmie W.
    - Haley, Harvey H.
    - Hall, Sidney
    - Hall, Nanette
    - Hall, T. O.
    - Hall, W. R.
    - Hall, Wallace
    - Halsey, Lacy Landreth
    - Hamilton, Janelle
    - Hamilton, Rebecca Pitts
    - Hamilton, Virginia
    - Hanes, Raenelle
    - Hanna, Paul R.
    - Hanner, Blanche
    - Hansard
    - Hanson, John J.
    - Hanson, Lois
    - Hanson, Rebakah
    - Haralambides, Theodoros
    - Harbin, Calvin Edward
    - Hargrove, James W.
    - Hariman, A.
    - Harman, Jeffye
    - Harmon, Joy
    - Harmon, Ray L.
    - Harmon, Virginia O.
    - Harrell, Daisy Estelle
    - Harrington, Mildred
    - Harris, Cora L.
    - Harris, D. G.
    - Harris, L. D.
    - Harris, Roy
    - Harriss, Elaine Akins
    - Harritt, J. Edward
    - Hartnett, Jan
    - Hart
    - Harville, Mary Jo
    - Harwell, Coleman
    - Haskins, Fleeta
    - Hasan, S. Hasndul
    - Hastings, Ben H.
    - Hatcher, Halene
    - Hatcher, Mildred
    - Hatcher, Virginia
    - Hatfield, Sam
    - Hausen, Vis, Jr.
    - Hawkes, H. Bourman
    - Hawkins, Hubert H.
    - Hawkins, Richard M.
    - Hawkins, Ulista
    - Hawkins
    - Hays, Brooks
    - Hays, Elsie
    - Headden, H. C.
    - Heald, Henry T.
    - Hebert, Arlis
    - Hebert, Joseph D., Jr.
    - Heflin, Lucille
    - Heflin
    - Heger, Alma
    - Heggerston, Adner
    - Heighsten
    - Hein, Constance
    - Heldring, Jerome
    - Hemphill, Martin
    - Henderson, Lois E.
    - Henderson, Sean
    - Hendrix, W. E.
    - Henry, Waights, G., Jr.
    - Herod, Audrey
    - Herring, Beverly
    - Herwig, Robert
    - Hester, Jean
    - Hester, Johnnia
    - Hester, Sue Martin
    - Hibbetts, Rowena
    - Hicks, Frances Ross
    - Hicks, Philip
    - Hiembaugh, Jean
    - Highberger, Ruth
    - Highsmith, E. M.
    - Hightower, Robert
    - Higman, Howard
    - Hildebrand, Betheny
    - Hiles, William G., Jr.
    - Hill, Carl
    - Hill, Henry H.
    - Hill, Horace Greeley, Jr.
    - Hill, J. A.
    - Hill, J. B.
    - Hill, John L.
    - Hill, Martha P.
    - Hill, Robert R.
    - Hill, Sallie
    - Hillman, James E.
    - Hillman, Patsy
    - Hiner, Mary Clay
    - Hinkley, Valerie Jannette
    - Hirabayaoki, Yashuhito
    - Hiratsuka, Masunori
    - Hirose, Hamako
    - Hirst, C. M.
    - Hobbs, Nicholas
    - Hobgood, B. E.
    - Hodges, Lucile Parsons
    - Hodges, Luther H.
    - Hodges, Roxanna Worth
    - Hodgson, Julia
    - Hoffman, Charles
    - Hoffman, Ruth
    - Hofwott, Clifford
    - Hogan, Mr. And Mrs.A. M.
    - Hogg, Henry T.
    - Hogge, James
    - Hoggard, Lara
    - Holbert, Charmaine
    - Holder, J. Newton
    - Hollabaugh, Johnanne
    - Holland, Kenneth
    - Hollingsworth, Samuel Hawkins, Jr.
    - Hollins, Barsha Gordon
    - Holloway, Otto
    - Holm, Mary Beth Mead
    - Holman, Lucile
    - Holmes, Brian
    - Holmes, E. N.
    - Holmes, Ethel
    - Holmes, George W.
    - Holroyd, Sarah
    - Holt, A. C.
    - Holt, Andrew
    - Holt
    - Hood, John
    - Hood, Margie
    - Hoover, Bob
    - Hoover, Herbert
    - Hoover, Oliver
    - Hope, Roy
    - Horn, J. Fred
    - Horn, Lizzie
    - Hoskins, A. B.
    - Hoskins
    - Houts, Jack
    - Houston, Mattie
    - Hovoris, John R.
    - Howard, Betty
    - Howard, Homer
    - Howard, Virginia
    - Howe, Latin
    - Howle, Eileen
    - Hoyt, Mildred D.
    - Hubbard, L. H.
    - Hubbell, Julia
    - Huck, Charlotte S.
    - Huddleston, James C.
    - Hudson, Irby
    - Hudson, Odelle
    - Huggins, Bernice
    - Hughes, Carlie
    - Hughes, Charles Evans
    - Hughes, Sara
    - Hugo, Grace
    - Hulfish, H. Gordon
    - Hull, J. W.
    - Humphreys, Clemit
    - Hunt, Charles
    - Hunt, Herold Christian
    - Hunt, Rolfe Lanier
    - Hunter, Eugenia
    - Hunter, H. Reid
    - Hunter, Lavinia
    - Hunter, Ruth
    - Hutchins, Robert
    - Hutchinson, Paul
    - Hutchison, Earl
    - Hutton, J. Warren
    - Hutts, Katie
  - I
    - Ihrke, Walter
    - Iida, Tomo
    - Ikard, Harriet
    - Ikenberry
    - Imaishi, Masuyuki
    - Inge, William
    - Ingrahan, Anna Ley
    - Ingram, Foy
    - Irby, Nolan M.
    - Isaaes, Howard
    - Ivey, John E.
    - Ivins, Lester Sylvan
    - Ivy, H. M.
  - J
    - Jackson, Walter
    - Jackson, William V.
    - Jaggers, C. H.
    - Jaggers, Gerald
    - James, Anne
    - Janessen, Clara Louise
    - Janin, Therese
    - Jarman, J. L.
    - Jarrell, Florence Anne
    - Jarrett, R. P.
    - Jenkins, F. C.
    - Jennings, Fay
    - Jennings, Jerry
    - Jennings, Joseph
    - Johe, E. R.
    - Johnson, Donald E.
    - Johnson, Henry
    - Johnson, Hobart
    - Johnson, Hugh
    - Johnson, Mrs. J. E.
    - Johnson, L. Margaret
    - Johnson, Lottie
    - Johnson, Lyndon Baines
    - Johnson, Mary Virginia
    - Johnson, Mayme A.
    - Johnson, Rayburn Whitson
    - Johnson, Raymond
    - Johnson, Victor, Jr.
    - Johnson, Violet
    - Johnson, Virginia
    - Jones, B. B.
    - Jones, Benjamin Willis
    - Jones, Children
    - Jones, Cynthia McCarlie
    - Jones, Dorothy
    - Jones, Douglas
    - Jones, Effie Butler
    - Jones, Frances Emily
    - Jones, Jennye Scott Bailey
    - Jones, Jesse H. (2)
    - Jones, Marie Kurz
    - Jones, Mary Gibbs
    - Jones, Mumford
    - Jones, Nancye
    - Jones, Patsy
    - Jones, Sam P.
    - Jones, W. C.
    - Jordon, Floyd
    - Jordon, Walter
    - Josepsson, B.
    - Judy, Jack
    - Judy, Ruth
    - Jurmon, Catherine
  - K
    - Kamikawa, Aigi
    - Kamikawa, Kiyo
    - Kane, Wyman
    - Kannard, Elizabeth
    - Karcher, Nancy
    - Karstaedo
    - Katahn, Enid
    - Kaufman, Max
    - Keel, Robert
    - Keen, Dorothy Ericsson
    - Kefauver, Estes
    - Keith, Margaret Lucille
    - Keller, J. P.
    - Keller, Lou
    - Kelley, Truman S.
    - Kellogg, W. K.
    - Kemner, Sue
    - Kenison, Ken
    - Kennamer, Laura
    - Kennamer, Lorrin G.
    - Kennedy, Fayna Crownover
    - Kennedy, John F.
    - Kennedy, T.
    - Kennedy, T. H.
    - Kenton, Egon
    - Kepler, Thomas S.
    - Keppel, F. P.
    - Keppel, Francis
    - Kerr
    - Keso, Edward
    - Ketcham, Walter
    - Ketten, Bernice L.
    - Kettner, Evelyn Wilkes Vail
    - Key
    - Keys, J. J.
    - Kidd, Kenneth
    - Kidder, Harold
    - Kilgore, Peggy
    - Killgore, Jean
    - Kilpatrick, William H
    - Kimball, Frank N.
    - Kincaid, Alene
    - King, A. C.
    - King, Helen
    - King, J. M.
    - King, J. Moore
    - King
    - Kiningham, Maggie Mai
    - Kinzer, John R.
    - Kipnis, Jgor
    - Kirby, Norene
    - Kirk, John R.
    - Kiser, Fannie B.
    - Kjer, Deel
    - Klatt, Dan
    - Klemer, Betty
    - Knapp, Seaman A.
    - Knight, David M.
    - Knight, Edgar W.
    - Knight, Frances
    - Knight, M. Violet
    - Knight, Margaret
    - Knobbs, Pauline
    - Knowles, Louise
    - Knowles, Olivia
    - Knuckles, James
    - Knudsen, Charles W.
    - Koepper, Robert C.
    - Kone, Florence
    - Koontz, Miriam E.
    - Koory, Charles
    - Kroll, Harry Harrison
    - Kuhlman, Clementina
    - Kurz, Marie
    - Kuykendall, Billie
    - Kyker, B. Frank
    - Kyle, Z. J.
  - L
    - Lacour, Elaine Theresa
    - Lacy, Berdie May
    - LaGrone, N.
    - Lahti, Taimi
    - Lamartino, G.
    - Lambert, Dimple
    - Lambird, Don K.
    - Lampson, John L.
    - Lancaster, Dan
    - Lance, Bess
    - Lance, Nandine
    - Lane, Marcetta
    - Lappin, R. B.
    - Larsen, Roy E.
    - Larson, Lewis J.
    - Larson, Tuttan
    - Lasseter
    - Lasty, Stuart
    - Latimer, Joseph Marion
    - Lavender, Leona
    - Law, Mouzon
    - Lawler, Nell
    - Lawrence, Gladwin
    - Lawrence, Walter S.
    - Lawrence, William
    - Lawrence, William
    - Lawson, Willie A.
    - Lawton
    - Lay, Elery A.
    - Lay, Herman
    - Layman, Charles M.
    - Layton, N. I.
    - Leavill, Ullin W.
    - Lee, Ann
    - Lee, Lulu
    - Lee, Ruth
    - Lee, Sheridan
    - Lee
    - Lefmoy, S. R.
    - Leftwich, Mary Fances
    - Leftwich, Rodney L.
    - Lehmann, Wilfred
    - Lelyveld, Arthur J.
    - Lemieux, Bruce Paul
    - Leonard, William H.
    - Lesley, J. B.
    - Lever
    - Lewis, Benjamin A.
    - Lewis, Beth
    - Lewis, John
    - Lewis, Tom
    - Ligon, LaNeta
    - Liles, Mary Edith
    - Liles, Parker
    - Lindley
    - Lindsay, Kenneth
    - Lindsey, Bell
    - Lindsey, Wilson
    - Lining, Catherine
    - Lining, Ora
    - Link, Gordon
    - Link, Mae M.
    - Little, Charles E.
    - Little, Harry A.
    - Little, Joe H.
    - Little, R. N.
    - Little, Thomas C.
    - Locker, Mary
    - Lockmiller, David A.
    - Lockwood, Charles M.
    - Loggins, Estelle
    - Long, C. G.
    - Long, Diane
    - Long, John Lawson
    - Lonier, Terry
    - Lounsbury, Elizabeth
    - Lovenstein, Meno
    - Lowden, Frank O.
    - Lowe, Enid Martha
    - Loy, Myrna
    - Lucas, Aileen
    - Lucas, M. G.
    - Lucas, Maurice
    - Luke, Ora M.
    - Luton, James N.
    - Lutz, C. M.
    - Lyons, Alice
    - Lyons, Lucile Manning
  - M
    - Ma, Shau Hing
    - MacLeish, Archibald
    - Maclin, Edward S.
    - Maclin, Margaret
    - MacManus, Seumas (2)
    - Madden, John T.
    - Magill, A. C.
    - Malin, Charles, Jr.
    - Mallory, Jasper Newton
    - Mallory, Jesse
    - Mallory, Virginia
    - Malone, Judy
    - Malone, Tennessee
    - Manchester
    - Maney, Henry
    - Mansfield, Agnes Adger
    - Manucci, Livio
    - Marani, Jean V.
    - Marple, Janie
    - Marrero-Vazquez, Jorge
    - Marshall, Wilmott
    - Martin, Bill, Jr.
    - Martin, Mrs. Buford
    - Martin, Helen
    - Martin, M. L.
    - Martin, Mary E.
    - Martin, Robert Lewis
    - Martin, Sue
    - Martin, Tommy
    - Mason, James Hocker
    - Massie, Robert K.
    - Masuoka, Ruth
    - Mathis, Florrie
    - Matthews, Glenda
    - Matthews, J. C.
    - Mattox, F. W.
    - Mattox, M. E.
    - Maxwell, Becky
    - Maxwell, C. J.
    - Maxwell, Howard
    - Maxwell, Richard
    - May, A. L.
    - Mayborn, Frank
    - Maybury, W. L.
    - Maybury
    - Mayfield, George, Jr.
    - McAllister, Teresa
    - McBride, Otis
    - McCain, Betty Jo
    - McCall, Duke K.
    - McCalla, Nelle Marie
    - McCan, Ada
    - McCann, Bess
    - McCarty, James W.
    - McCaskill
    - McClain-Nolen, Mary Frances
    - McClanahan, Dorothy
    - McClaren, Knox, Jr.
    - McClellan, Mrs. B. B.
    - McClellen, Glenn
    - McClister, Lena
    - McCluer, Leon
    - McClure, C. H.
    - McClurkin, William
    - McConnel, M.
    - McConnell, Anita
    - McConnell, Freeman E.
    - McCracken, Jewell
    - McCracken, Sarah
    - McCraney, Jean
    - McDaniel, Alta C.
    - McDill, Janie
    - McDonald, Jessie Everette
    - McDonald, John D.
    - McDonald, Marcia
    - McDonald, R. C.
    - McDonald, Ruth
    - McDonald, Tom
    - McDonough, Thomas E.
    - McElroy, E.
    - McElroy, Neil
    - McEwen, Bill
    - McGehee, J. D.
    - McGinnis, Howard J.
    - McGlothlin, Mary Louise
    - McGlothlin, William J.
    - McGrath, Earl J.
    - McKeawn, Boyd
    - McKee, Clyde V.
    - McKee
    - McKinney, Lillian
    - McKnight, Lee
    - McKnight, O. E.
    - McLaughlin
    - McLemore, R. A.
    - McMahon, John Julia
    - McMahon, Otis
    - McMullen, Edgar
    - McMurry, Charles A.
    - McMurry, Tom Roy
    - McNair, Robert
    - McNee
    - McNeil, Carolyn
    - McNulty, Mary
    - McQuistion, Ed
    - McQuistion, Fred
    - McQuitty, Robert
    - McSwain, Dorothy
    - McSwain, Eldridge T.
    - McVoy, Mrs. L. C.
    - Mead, Margaret
    - Meade, Mrs. George P.
    - Meadows, J. B.
    - Meadows, Leon
    - Meadows
    - Means, Marie Hackl
    - Measemer, M. B.
    - Meeks, Elizabeth Lorraine
    - Menees, Rubye
    - Merrill, Charlie
    - Messmore, Evelyn
    - Meyer, A. C.
    - Meyer, A. R.
    - Meyer, Ethel June
    - Michelson, Don
    - Mikell, H. J.
    - Miller, Charles S.
    - Miller, James L., Jr.
    - Miller, Lucile Gardner
    - Miller, Patricia
    - Miller, Ruth
    - Millican, Carl
    - Milling, C. L.
    - Mills, James O.
    - Mills, Mary Elizabeth
    - Millwood, Pat
    - Mims, Edwin
    - Mims, Jimmie
    - Minsky, Henri
    - Minssen, Lucillia
    - Misner, Paul J.
    - Mitchell, Ben
    - Mitchell, Claire
    - Mitchell, Dora May
    - Mitchell, Hobart
    - Mitchell, Jane
    - Mitchell, John G.
    - Mitchell, Sally
    - Mitchell
    - Mixson, Elizabeth
    - Mobley, Vera Grace
    - Moffitt, Orvil Lee
    - Moncrief, Irene
    - Monhollon, Patsy P.
    - Montague, Sallie J.
    - Montgomery, Olive
    - Moody, Stanley
    - Moody, William P.
    - Moog
    - Moon, family
    - Mooney, Mary Sue
    - Moore, Clardy H.
    - Moore, Clyde B.
    - Moore, Conrad
    - Moore, Mrs. Earl A.
    - Moore, H. Claude
    - Moore, Hollis
    - Moore, Lena
    - Moore, Malvin Earl
    - Moore, Nannie Lee
    - Moore, Norman
    - Moore, Thomas Earl
    - Moreland, J. E.
    - Morelock, H. W.
    - Morgan, Amon Livingston
    - Morgan, Cecil
    - Morgan, Joe
    - Morgan, Kenimer H.
    - Morgan, Warren M.
    - Morris, Joe
    - Morris, Sarah Croom
    - Morrison, Ralph
    - Morrison, Wilbur Cyrus
    - Morriss, Burney
    - Morrissey, Jimmy
    - Morse, Wayne
    - Mort, Paul R.
    - Mortin, Virginia
    - Morton, Arnold
    - Morton, Ben A.
    - Morton, David
    - Morton, Mary
    - Mosley, Joel Rufus
    - Moss, J. E.
    - Moss, Oveda M.
    - Mott, Edith
    - Moultrie, James
    - Mulloy, William Anderson
    - Mumpower, Don
    - Muncie, Virginia
    - Murphy, Charles Martin
    - Murphy, Irene
    - Murphy, Jeanne M.
    - Murrell
    - Myers, Chuck
  - N
    - Nadler, Marcus
    - Nagiduff, Nila
    - Napier, T. H.
    - Nash, Corrine Y.
    - Neal, Harry
    - Neelameghau, Arashanapalai
    - Nees, Virginia
    - Neff, Elizabeth
    - Neil, Robert
    - Neil, Ronald J.
    - Nelms, Sara Barbara
    - Nelson, B. B.
    - Nelson, Charles
    - Nelson, Edward G.
    - Neu, C. T.
    - Neuman, Alice
    - Newbroagh
    - Newhall, Margaret
    - Newman, J. Marion
    - Newman, Linda
    - Newman, Mamie
    - Newport, Rosalyn
    - Newsom, Carl R.
    - Newton, Shirley
    - Newton, Thomas Edward
    - Ng, Kook Chin
    - Nichols, Ralph G.
    - Nicholson, Marion
    - Nicholson, W. B.
    - Niell, Betty
    - Nigh, Sam
    - Niles, John Jacob
    - Nishizaki, Takako
    - Noah, Max
    - Noble, Janet McGinnis
    - Nolan, Sara
    - Nooe, Roger T.
    - Norden, Laurel
    - Norman, loyal V.
    - Norris, Raymond C.
    - Northcutt, Hudie L.
    - Norton, Doris
    - Notter, Frances Clarona
    - Notwood, Pat
    - Nourse, Lyda
    - Noys, La Verne
    - Nungster, Frances
  - O
    - Oakley, Bethel
    - O’Beirne Uta Ramm
    - Obenchain, J. R.
    - O’Brien, Bernice
    - Odom, P.
    - Ogden, Ruth
    - Olive, William H.
    - Oliver, Marjorie
    - Olmstead, Clarence
    - Olson, Clara M.
    - Oman, Catherine
    - Ordway, Martha
    - O’Rear, John William
    - Orr, M. L.
    - Osborne, Elizabeth Macdonald
    - O’Steen, Alton
    - Overby, James
    - Owen, Mary A.
    - Owsley
    - Oxnam, G. Bromly
  - P
    - Pace, Virginia L.
    - Pack, Brenda
    - Page, Charles
    - Page, Elizabeth
    - Panowski, Rose
    - Paris, John T.
    - Parisot, Aldo
    - Parker, Alice
    - Parker, Franklin
    - Parker, Hilary D.
    - Parker, Pauline
    - Parks, Annie Grace
    - Parks, Betty
    - Parks, N. L.
    - Parman, Mildred
    - Parr, Asa George
    - Parrish, Annie C.
    - Parrish, Daisy Terry
    - Parrish, Ela W.
    - Parson, Ora Lucile
    - Partain, William
    - Patrick, Martha
    - Patterson, Don S.
    - Patterson, Mabel Grey
    - Patton, Dorothy Edwards
    - Payne, Bruce Ryburn
    - Payne, Carr
    - Payne, Frances Cooper
    - Payne, William H.
    - Peacock, Otis L.
    - Pearl, Minnie
    - Pearson, Beverly
    - Peeler, Grady
    - Penrod, James Herschel
    - Percy, Richard
    - Pereda, Eugene
    - Perry, Caroline
    - Perry, Penelope Virginia
    - Phelps, Jewell
    - Phelps, John
    - Phelps, Regina
    - Phillips, Burrill
    - Phillips, David Brandon
    - Phillips, Doris
    - Phillips, H. D.
    - Phillips, Pauline W.
    - Phillips, Ray C.
    - Phillips, Ruby M.
    - Phillips, Wendell S.
    - Phipps, W. E.
    - Picknell, Frances
    - Pierce, Bertha
    - Pierce, Joan
    - Piers, Ellen Virginia
    - Pinkston, Eva G.
    - Pippin, Eileen
    - Pitts, Ollie Polk
    - Pleasants, James G.
    - Pledger, Maud Myrtice
    - Ponder, J. Andrew
    - Pope, Necie
    - Poret, G. C.
    - Porter, Frances Ellen
    - Porter, Jean
    - Porter, Richard
    - Porterfield, Hazel V.
    - Posey, Hugh
    - Poteat, Edwin McNeill
    - Potts, Aurelia B.
    - Potts, Barbara
    - Powell, William F.
    - Powers, Sue McFall
    - Pratt, Daniel
    - Priest, C. P.
    - Priestley, Herschel
    - Priestley, James
    - Prince, Hayden Peter
    - Pritchett, Katherine M.
    - Pritchett, Margaret
    - Pruett, Haskell
    - Pruett, Mildred
    - Puckett, Marian
    - Pugsley, James W.
    - Pulliam, Roy A.
    - Punaro, Rae
    - Purdy, Elmo
    - Purser, Stuart
    - Pyburn, Nita Katherine
    - Pyle, Billy Wayne
  - Q
    - Qualls, Fred
    - Quezada, Humberto
    - Quigley
  - R
    - Rackley, J. Ralph
    - Rademacher, Eva
    - Ragan, Wendy
    - Ragsdale, Warner
    - Ramer, Earl A.
    - Ramsey, Hiden
    - Ramsey, J. N.
    - Ramsey, J. W.
    - Ramsey, Mary Margaret
    - Rawlins, G. M.
    - Rawls, Flora
    - Ray, J. J.
    - Ray, Miriam
    - Ray, Vera
    - Raybourn, Loreese
    - Raye, Marcia Ann
    - Rayfield, Florence
    - Reale, Ida
    - Rebarker, Herbert
    - Reed, Donna Lee
    - Reed, Katherine
    - Reed, Helen
    - Reed, Nancy
    - Reeder, Glen P.
    - Reichert, Victor
    - Reid, J. W.
    - Reilly, Alma Parry
    - Remley, Roxie
    - Renfroe, Carl G.
    - Replogle, Vernon
    - Revercrombie, Mary H.
    - Reynolds, Earl A.
    - Reynolds, T. H.
    - Reynolds, Tommie
    - Rhea, Laura McGowan
    - Riatt, Ann
    - Rice, Carmine
    - Rice, Elizabeth
    - Rice, Earl C.
    - Richardson, Anne
    - Richardson, Gilbert P.
    - Richardson, Nancy
    - Richardson
    - Richmond
    - Rickey, Branch
    - Rideout, Walter B.
    - Riggan, Frances Ione
    - Riggs, Katherine Hackworth
    - Rigsby, Kyle C.
    - Riley, Bessie P.
    - Rinsland, Henry D.
    - Rivenborn, J. T.
    - Roberts, B. H.
    - Roberts, Edwina
    - Robinette, Charles
    - Robinson, Ellen
    - Robinson, Glen
    - Robinson, J. R.
    - Robinson, Lucy
    - Robinson, N.
    - Robinson, Norma Lou
    - Robinson, Ruth
    - Robinson, Virginia
    - Robison, R. M., Jr.
    - Rockefeller, John D.
    - Rodriguez, Jose
    - Rodgers, Mary Elizabeth
    - Roehm, Dan
    - Roehm, Paul A.
    - Roehm, Tyler Alfred
    - Roemer, Joseph
    - Rogers, Mrs. C. E.
    - Rogers, E. G.
    - Rogers, Faye
    - Rogers, Lois
    - Rogers, Mary D.
    - Rogers, Sharon
    - Roland, H. I.
    - Roller, Bert
    - Roller, Elizabeth
    - Rollins, Hazel
    - Romersa, Henry
    - Romine, William Bethel
    - Rondelbush
    - Root, Elihu
    - Rose, Albert
    - Rose, Julia
    - Roth
    - Rothacker
    - Rowan, Albia
    - Rowe, John L.
    - Rowlett, Patricia
    - Rowland, Minnie Lee
    - Rowson, Sarah
    - Rubens, Fred
    - Rush, Jane
    - Russell, Bertrand
    - Russell, Joe L.
    - Rustin, John W.
    - Rutkowski, Walt
    - Ryan, Jessie L.
  - S
    - Sachar, Abram Leon
    - Sackett, Santa
    - Sagastume, Lisandro
    - Salmon, Parley W.
    - Salmon, W. T.
    - Salners, Jean Overton
    - Samonial, Ann Love
    - Sancis, Corrine
    - Sanders, C. F.
    - Sanders, D. W.
    - Sanders, Edward A.
    - Sanders, Jennings B.
    - Sandford, Edward T.
    - Sandford, Terry
    - Sandlin, Monte